Hey, Will. Chris Perkins from the South
Florida Suns Sentinel. Congratulations.
>> Thank you. I appreciate that.
>> Hey, tell me about um your value. You
know, we know that you are a uh a
blocking tight end, but you seem like
you have some good hands also. This
seems like a good place for you because
they want to run the ball. Tell me about
your value to the NFL and your value to
the Dolphins. Uh what what you think it
both are.
>> I mean, you kind of hit on it a little
bit. Um, I think I'm a dominant uh run
blocker. I think I'm a, you know, a
dominant uh blocker at the point of
attack, but um, I don't think people
give me enough credit for my passing
ability. Um, I was using an offense with
tons of weapons. So, um, opportunities
were are limited, but um, whenever I got
the ball, like you said, I had sure
hands. I caught it and I made the most
of it. So,
>> and and tell me about uh, attitude. uh
you know this this Dolphins regime with
John Eric Sullivan the GM and Jeff
Heftley the coach they want physicality
they want aggression they want to run
the ball how do you fit into that mold
>> yeah I mean um I think mentality the
aggression is you know 90% of the game I
think you need to have that to impose
your will on you know other players and
wear them down throughout the game
you're not going to win the game after
one play so I think it's important to
again wear down players and this is
something I've you know had my entire
life that mentality Um, I play with a
switch, you know, on the field. I mean,
you see, you check out the film, that's
how I play, but off the field, I feel
like I'm a pretty, you know, genuine,
you know, guy that doesn't have too too
many enemies. So,
>> right, cool, man. Thanks. Appreciate it.
>> Yeah, absolutely.
>> David,
>> hey, will David Feronus, also from the
South Florida Sun. Congratulations.
>> Thank you.
>> So, uh, Kaden Proctor, the Dolphins
first round pick, said, and I quote,
"We're going to run the out of the
ball."
>> Oh, yeah. Yeah, drafting you in the
third seems to fall in line with
choosing him in the first. What do you
think of the identity this new Dolphins
regime is trying to establish with
players like yourself and Proctor on the
offensive side?
>> Yeah, I mean I think it's pretty clear.
I mean, like you said, I mean, he's a
power powerful run blocker and I think
of that of myself. So, you know, you
pair us two together, I think we're
going to move some, you know, defensive
line and I think that's going to be our
identity.
>> Cool. Awesome. I appreciate it.
>> Yep.
Isaiah
>> going on. Well, Isaiah Smalls from Miami
Herald. How are you?
>> Good. Pretty good. I'm feeling good
right now. So,
>> that's what's up. That's what's up. I
wanted to ask a little bit about the
mentality of of run blocking. I think
that takes a special type of person to
commit to that, especially in day and
age where a lot of tight ends want to
catch the ball, go up field, etc., etc.,
etc. So, just kind of walk me through
why you've leaned into uh this this uh
run blocking identity. Yeah. Uh, I mean,
I played a bunch of sports growing up.
Um, I've played against a lot of tough
competition. I feel like I just kind of
figured out um to be successful, you
need that mentality and, you know, not a
lot of people like to, you know, go to
that, you know, that area. But, I think
it's important and could really wear
down the opponent. And again, that's
something I take pride in and it's
something I definitely uh, you know,
hang my head on is my mentality. and uh
again just imposing imposing you know
your will on someone else.
>> And then obviously you're part of that
team that won the national championship
um in 2024. Just what was that
experience like and what did you learn
that you hope to take to Miami?
>> Yeah. No, absolutely. I mean I never
thought I would be in that position. Um
I started at Ohio and then transferring
to Ohio State the first season I went
there I won at Natty. So it's just cool
how things play out. And then again,
just being in this situation right now,
I think, you know, I've gone through the
levels of football and I just think it's
something that, you know, it's just the
next level and, you know, I have to
adapt to it like any other level, but
you know, once you get there, you know,
just, you know, take off running with
it.
>> Cool. Appreciate you. Congratulations.
>> Thank you,
>> Travis.
>> Hey, what's up, Will? Congrats and
welcome to Miami, man.
>> Thank you. I appreciate it.
>> You talked about playing multiple sports
a little I saw you were a lacrosse
player back in your day. How do you
think that helped to translate onto the
football field?
>> Um, I think just overall footwork. Um, I
mean, I'm a, you know, a taller guy and
then lacrosse there's not, you know, the
biggest guys playing. They're usually
quicker guys. I was a defender. So, I
think just, um, being able to move with
those guys and, you know, stay in front
of them. And again, just footwork. And
then I think lacrosse is a great game
just competitively. I mean, they say
it's the fastest game on two feet and um
again, just it puts you in a lot of
situations to where um it's you versus
somebody else and and and then again,
just working with the team. So, that
footwork comment is interesting because
you did so many things in terms of roles
as a blocker at Ohio State, whether you
were Hback attached to the to the line
of scrimmage or out in space. I'm
curious with all those different
assignments that you got, how did you
approach the like preparing for
different blocking angles, different
assignments, you know, digging out
defensive tackles, kicking out the end
of the man line of scrimmage. What was
your process like for getting ready for
all that you did at Ohio State?
>> Yeah, I mean, I was fortunate to play
with a lot of, uh, um, really good OC's.
I mean, uh, two years ago I was with
Chip Kelly and he's super creative. So,
you never knew what you're going to get
at practice the next day. You know, he's
putting you in the back field. We got 14
personnel. you got so many different
jobs and um it's just cool to be able to
um be trusted in those positions. Uh
like you said, whether it's in the back
field, on the ball, in the hip or you
know, split out. So um I think it's just
a lot of it is just trust and then um I
mean every day of practice we rep
everything cuz again you never know what
you're going to get. So
>> that's awesome. Thanks Will and congrats
again man.
>> Thanks
>> Chris.
>> Hey Will. Chris Perkins again. Um, tell
me about the challenge of going to Ohio
State and at the risk of sounding
ridiculous, why? Um, because you could
have stayed at Ohio. Was was stepping up
in competition a factor? Was NIL a
factor? Why why'd you go?
>> Um, I think just to where I wanted to go
and, you know, reach my maximum
potential. I think, um, entering the
portal was, you know, best in my favor.
Nothing against Ohio. I loved Ohio. I
mean, I love all those coaches. You
know, I left on good terms, but I think
just to where I wanted to go and to be
against the best competition, I had to,
you know, make that uh make that leap.
And uh definitely wasn't easy. It was uh
you know, um it was definitely a shot in
the dark, but you know, it worked out.
There was a spot open at Ohio State with
um you know, Cade leaving, Kate Stover.
So, filling that role and then you know,
just proving to the team that I'm meant
to be there and then just running with
the opportunity. It was kind of my
mentality.
And you got to have a a good amount of
confidence in yourself, right? Ohio
State, I mean, they could bring in a
fivestar, they could get another guy out
of the transfer portal, right? You have
to be confident to go to Ohio State.
Yeah. Yeah.
>> And I feel like my entire life I've
always been in these situations to where
like I mean I was a twoar DN coming out
of high school and then was fortunate to
play at Ohio and then again fortunate to
play at Ohio State. So, I think just,
you know, getting to the level at each
level is um something, you know, I do.
And I think again, I'm a good fit for
the Dolphins.
>> All right. Thanks. Congratulations
again.
>> Thank you,
>> David.
>> Hey, Will. David again. Yeah, you
mentioned being a good fit for the
Dolphins. Uh the past four seasons under
Mike McDaniel, they ran a lot of outside
zone. Uh some continuity on the
offensive side with Bobby Slowick still
being on the staff now as OC. So, uh,
how much do you enjoy outside zone, the
that blocking scheme, and, um, you just
how do you think you you, uh, perform in
that setting?
>> No, I love it. Uh, we got into that a
lot, um, throughout the season last
year. Um, I was on front side a lot and
I feel like I really figured out, you
know, the different combinations and
different looks and what to expect. And
that's something I'm definitely
comfortable with. Um, ran a lot of
counter. So again, I mentioned, you
know, playing different positions,
playing off the ball again, front side.
Um, just being to do all that and being
trust at the point of attack is, you
know, something I feel confident in.